it says if you encounter the sarcas
sarcasm tag take a deep breath and move
along is what it says dude I like how is
the HTML 5 spec actually an engaging
read
[Music]
like
wow this has been a whirlwind man it
really this year cannot slow down can it
no it can't dude we um here we are we
are in Miami for the recording the
second episode I think this one's gonna
air first though um yeah we we recorded
an episode day before yesterday with
Yousef samuda and man is that a good
episode you guys are in for a good one
next week oh man it was funny because I
was joking with uh with some people that
were like oh were were you on uh
yousef's podcast yesterday I was like
yeah I was I was the guest actually dude
seriously it was so good and uh just a
lot of really high technical bugs a lot
of great discussions surrounding um
client side constraints in the browser
and that sort of thing um so really
looking forward to airing that episode
and I gotta relisten to it myself yeah
dude I mean it's so awesome like seeing
somebody who has I I mean it feels like
a niche right but it's a web it's just
like web hacking right he he has managed
to like Corner this niche of like atos
and post message and like deep
JavaScript bugs and you do that too man
like don't get me wrong like but uh yeah
so so I guess one of the some of the
things that I kind of want to talk about
is takeaways from this live hacking
event um uh the the target is public it
is Capital One yep um and it's been a
really fun event uh a lot of client side
bugs have have rolled out especially for
me um so there's there's a couple good
takeaways there and and one of those is
that
I I wasn't paying enough attention to
client side routing I I don't think
before this specific event and like I've
been predicting over the past couple
months or or even maybe a year at this
point since we started the podcast um
clientside path traversal is just going
to continue to grow and grow and grow as
a bug class and we've seen that at this
event we've seen it at past events
paying attention to client side routing
is going to be the new SE surf in in the
near future yeah absolutely because
there there are so many levels of
complexity now with just like browsers
like how the browser is handling
requests that you are going to have to
rely on client side path rsal at a
certain point right like
CF within the next 10 years could not
even exist anymore it's going to be real
tricky when the browsers remove the the
same site lack default um sort of uh
caveat that they have the the the top
level navigation with a post request
within 2 minutes of the cookie being set
when when that goes away um it's going
to be very hard to implement CFS
um by default these could it's going to
be safe which which is great for the
community but a little bit sad for us
yeah um and and so definitely those
client side passers are going to
continue to be a thing and and I've seen
um this event um and and past events as
well a lot of really interesting stuff
surrounding you chaining those client
side path traversals with open redirects
and then actually being able to control
content that's being placed into the
application that the application expects
to be secure right you know they they're
trusting their API respons you know
requests and and you're going to get
stuff back and sometimes it's HTML in a
Json blob and then they literally just
dump it right into the Dom yeah and
you've just got xss so um especially
when it can be trained with an open
redirect a lot of impact there yeah
absolutely um so where did you spend
most of your time on the
event man I jumped I jumped all over the
place there was there was a couple
things in scope um that that that went
out of scope uh by a certain time so I
went and focused on the things that were
time sensitive first and then for the
rest of the event man I was just kind of
chugging away on on client side stuff um
I've got
40 bless my heart I've got 40 bugs right
now 40 and I was up till 3:00 a.m. last
night um finding another high uh and
getting it submitted and getting it
fully exploited so I'm I am toasty right
now but I'm expecting some good results
I'm a little bit nervous right now
though man cuz it's like let's the event
has officially closed and they've only
paid 150k I think the last time we
looked at it and they might be paying
them out right now as we're recording
yeah yeah 150k yeah so I I I I think
that they're they're lagging a little
bit behind on this so I'm I'm interested
to see how it turns out tonight yeah I
have a feeling it'll probably end at
least 3 or 400k total bounties that's
what I think at least yeah um I think a
lot of it is there was so many
especially on those time sensitive areas
like like you said like I remember I
checked on the first day and there was
like 5 or 10 people who had 25 reports
in and I was like oh okay I need a new
time zone like wow this is crazy um
crazy and for those of you that aren't
familiar with the live hacking event
sort of set up um how it works in these
competition is there's a dupe period for
the first uh week of hacking so you've
got all these top hackers hacking on one
Target and then you know the bounties
are in at and uh and then but obviously
there's going to be a lot of dupes
because a lot of the top Packers are
going to find similar bugs so um within
that first week all of the bounties that
are are dupes are all split evenly
between all the reporters um so it's
very important within that first week to
find all of the things that you can find
that you think are not specifically you
know Rhino raater bugs or techno geek
bugs right right and and get those
submitted get those in before the due
period ends and then you can kind of
focus on the bigger brain stuff right
yeah yeah and I did a I did a similar
approach so there was there was a flag
that they had set out um in the mobile
apps I was like well that's that's my
that's my jam so let me go all right
here we go yeah so I went in on that I
got that super quick U I think I I think
I got it it hasn't been paid out yet got
first I'm pretty sure I got it um and
then uh I kind of made a a well it was a
mistake but I didn't know it at the time
where I spent most of my time on the
mobile apps and again because my Niche
right so I you know I was talking with
reso he was like you know what dude just
do it like focus in going in it'll be
worth it I was like okay I'll do it and
so I started tracking my time this time
this was the first event I tracked my
amount of time I haed oh man you you
were going seriously I was going serious
honestly it really helped with like I
don't know maybe it's just my ADHD but
like having a timer where like if I feel
like I've been doing something for a bit
and just being able to like look up and
see oh like I'm two hours in or three
hours in or whatever like it's good to
feel like I'm making progress and not
just like I'm sitting still there's
something about putting the hours in
that that's gratifying in of itself
right right um but unfortunately I
didn't I didn't didn't find anything
else other than that I found like one
low and got close in the mobile app was
tight man very tight and we and even
across the other mobile hackers I think
there were only like one or two other
accepted reports on the mobile app scope
so that's uh that that was definitely um
sad to see you know yeah they had a ton
of obfuscation on it I spent a bunch of
time getting around that I thought you
know oh for sure like once I get past
this obfuscation good like I'm gonna
find all the bugs as soon as I get past
this I got past it at like hour six and
oh my gosh was just like testing end
points looking for other entry points
like looking for anything and just
nothing panned out I even uh pulled out
the full list of end points I sent them
over to reso he was like all right let
me fuzz these nothing so wow dude yeah
that's that's that's just how the cards
Li and I know we were going to do a uh
what did you put in the chat hacker
therapy hacker therapy session man so
like how did that make you feel Joel
that moment I'm not going to lie I was
like like in the Heat of the Moment I
was like you know what maybe I'm done
with bug Bounty like dude I know man I
always feel that way and then it's like
it you know it pulls you back in to you
know when you find something that and
we've got we've got a bug we've got an
atto on a specific site that we need to
go finish up yeah so maybe after this
event we'll we'll go do that and that'll
kind of Swing us back around into into
the proper got to get that momentum you
know man mindset grind set yeah dude but
I will say the nice thing about tracking
the time I felt like because I knew how
many hours I put in I felt less bad when
I decided it was time to cut my losses
and so when I was like okay I'm at 25
hours on this mobile app I'm done on the
mobile app I'm not I'm not spending more
time on this if I'm GNA hack more on on
this target I'm GNA look at other scope
assets because this is no longer worth
my time if I'm going to find anything
it's not going to be on these abs yeah I
I I've got a I've got a cool story about
learning how to cut your losses this
event I I found what should have been a
bug but was not a bug there was a um
there was a specific uh spot in the in
one of the applications where it was
taking a parameter via the hash and uh
it was taking that parameter it was
actually doing a domain validation on a
different parameter and then using this
parameter as the API host okay for for
like their fetch stuff that they would
do s bug bug like this in the past oh
did you really and um but that here's
the thing with that so typically this
would be an easy easy dub be but um
there was a there's CSP in place a
connect Source CSP okay so that means I
can't connect to any website that is not
what they had to find they've got one
website uh in scope they've got self and
then they had star. googleapis.com okay
that's pretty broad that is so I was
looking into that I was like okay what
can I do with that and lo and behold the
storage uh API for or the way you access
Google storage buckets y um the S3
buckets of of Google Cloud is on
storage. googleapis.com I was like great
I'll just upload a Json file to a bucket
and then um you know if I need to do
multiple request I can like get the
timing right uh you know and I can
change out the file and that sort of
thing so far nothing has gone wrong
so like this is great list but here's
that's the problem right because I go
all the way down this this this you know
path and then it doesn't work at the end
so so I'll tell you I'll tell you so all
right I plug it in there give it to host
it sends out the request boo Bo
um Access Control uh headers for need to
be in place so you need access control
allow origin header I'm like okay
on the bucket on the bucket so I was
like okay uh you know Google storage
bucket Access Control header right no
okay well first actually I had a
different idea first I was like okay
maybe I I can just use a data URL okay
right oh yeah yeah right actually yeah
yeah why not right and I was like okay
great and I I opened up my browser I
said fetch data URL and it worked and I
was like oh wow I can I didn't know that
I could use a data URL with Fetch and I
can specify the content type and
everything I was like this is really
cool where do you specify content type
in the data you itself it's like data
you know colon and then it say like text
like text or application Json or
whatever and then basic appes when it
fetches it to yeah and it does it's
clean CSP doesn't like data of course I
I don't know what I was thinking but I
was really I was really um interested to
that that like oh wow I can I can use a
data URI with fetch so anyway then I go
to the bucket solution right and so okay
I need to solve the access control L
origin header problem so I start
googling that and there's a way to set
it for the bucket I'm like hell yeah so
I go ahead and upload the thing and it
and I'm like all right you know I got it
set to Star whatever no problem okay and
I send it up and it's Bo
Boop this request this fetch request is
with mode send credentials so there
needs to be an access control allow
credentials true header in the response
and you can't set that for Google
storage buckets but wait Joel it gets
better man okay okay listen to this
dude then I'm like what how do I
fix this problem so I start researching
researching researching also on storage.
googleapis.com is the Json API for the
storage uh interface so you can get like
metadata on objects and stuff like that
okay that one does return uh it echoes
the the origin into the access control
allow origin header that work and and
and it has access control allow
credentials true so it's like this is
perfect but how do I get my arbitrary
arbitrary data in there right because
it's the metadata URL it's not actually
or it's the metadata endpoint it's not
the actual content well there's this one
weird parameter that says instead of
giving the metadata for this object
return the actual object content and I'm
like yes this is perfect I got it and
there's a sync too there's a window
location.href sync that's right after
the call so it's it literally if it has
a Json attribute then it just puts puts
it right into window location. I'm like
hell yeah this is xss let's go I mean at
this point so far you I'm I'm are you
pranking me like down no no ups and down
ups and downs man and then guess
what I send it in JavaScript URI boooop
CSP script
Source can't execute anything I I don't
know why I didn't see it I went on this
whole thing there's no script source and
and I just it's a dead end you can't do
anything with it there's no there's no
JavaScript you can execute I I've tried
this and that and the other thing here's
the other thing it caches the API host
in session storage okay and then it will
use that for another request that that
has sensitive information in the URL so
I'm like great I can link that but when
it sends the sensitive information via
the URL it clears session storage so
it's like in session storage supposed to
be per tab I figured out a way to get
that to not work right to to cash mine
and then use it on the page okay
it's still it's still freaking they they
clear session storage so I can't leak
the data it's useless wow okay I was
going to ask a couple things if you
tried before I found out about the CSP I
was going to say um I was going to
wonder if you had tried redirects for
the storage bucket thing to see if you
could maybe redirect it to the URL you
wanted or at like Rapid or something but
no no now the the connect source is
going to block anything and there's no
way for you to make that initial
connection because you can't make CP
right uh you know do or a storage dot um
what about like CSS like CSS
exfiltration yeah but you we have
no no no there's no there's no way to
inject so then then there's also sort of
a way for you to get HTML injection but
it's in angular's HTML injection thing
so it's just totally it's it's it's
impossible man I've had six people look
at it at the event and all of them are
extremely talented client side hackers
not a man dang so anyway man so
disappointing I I I'll be honest with
you I sunk probably eight hours into
that in um and that was a mistake you
know I I got the full length that I made
it in the
end three hours in probably and I made
that extra hop to oh okay maybe I can
leak data via this you know poisoning
the API host in session
storage maybe five or six in you know so
maybe that you know if that clear
session storage thing wasn't there then
maybe I could have actually gotten the
exploitation but one of the hardest
things in bug Bounty for me man is
knowing when to cut your losses for real
and I just suck at that and and maybe
sometimes that makes us better hackers
and maybe that makes us pops bugs but I
think a lot of time it makes us
lose lose a lot of time right and like
it's a trade-off right because there's
always like if you cut your losses too
early then you definitely could miss
something there's like you guarantee the
Miss right like yeah I mean assuming
something's there but yes like the the m
is significantly more but like equally
if you keep hacking the Miss also like
the other scope and the other things
that you haven't looked at like that
miss is still there um and I I dude I
I've been thinking about this because I
like I don't know if I should adjust
anything and I don't think I should
like because I don't think I did
anything wrong maybe maybe I should have
cut losses maybe a little earlier
maybe I should have spent less time on
like the nitty-gritty of of the off fisc
and stuff but what I would say Joel is
25 hours is I mean you got a full-time
job as well yeah so that I I wasn't
really considering that I I 25 hours is
not where I cut my losses in in normally
in these sort of situations but I I
didn't really take into consideration
the fact that you have you know limited
time constraints with with your fulltime
job with full-time job I was doing about
six hours a day I had yeah that's that's
that's yeah that's that's yeah so you
know it is what it is um you know you
can't win them all I think I I've said
that to like 10 people at this event so
you know it it happens and um I think
I'm just going to apply the same you
know go deep right like that's what we
always say go deep keep going keep going
deep just keep going deep and and notes
right like I was taking a ton of notes
and by the end of it I was looking
through my notes and I was like I have
nothing else to look at here dud we need
to find that every time I I say going
deep in uh in with a bug Bounty context
I think of that tweet by Tom Nom Nom do
you know the one I'm talking about no no
no no so dude he somebody like tweeted
out a I'll have to see if I can find it
but it's like one of the most legendary
tweets I've ever seen someone was like
all right bug Bounty tips you know go
deep read the
manual uh you know push hard something
like that and then Tom comment and a
bunch of other ones that are in line and
then Tom comments he's like this is also
my approach to sex
oh my God and I'm like dude you're nuts
this is such that it ratioed hard of
course you know it's just amazing I
think it was HCK luk I think it was
hack um yeah man getting intimate with
the application as we say uh is is
pivotal um to these sort of things uh so
yeah and I will say man I am uh I am I
am intimate with many of the
applications right now and I I'm I'm
really looking forward to uh not looking
at a computer screen for a little while
I'm going going out of the country right
after this um which is which will be
great uh good time to relax and I'm just
hoping these these bugs pay out the way
the way they should yeah absolutely dude
I I heard what your total is right now
versus what you were expecting and I was
like it's GNA be a little tricky man I'm
looking my at my phone because I'm like
uh you know and and then the thing is
about these the the events too is you
know it'll they'll make like a ch-ching
sound if you're downstairs you know in
the hacking room and you'll get the you
know the pings and stuff like that so
it's very like dopamine heavy you know
yeah very inator yeah so um any other
any other
cool takeaways from the event for you
the only other thing that comes to my
very tired brain right now is I've I was
very impressed with a specific set of
business logic bugs from Douglas day uh
Archangel at this event he really took
his methodology and he normally collabs
we call you know we did an episode with
him we called him the king of
collaboration he did a solo um a solo
event this time yep and I was talking to
him about some of his bugs and they're
just elegant yeah you know and it just
it it exemplifies perfectly the idea of
understanding
what it exemplifies two things
understanding the business and hitting
them at their pain points and and really
setting a goal for the application the
other one is setting a goal for the
application and just you know brooding
it into having that goal yeah D um which
is something that we talk about a good
bit so I think he did a really good job
with this I'm hoping he gets the payouts
that he deserves at the specific one
yeah um but you know we've got time to
argue afterwards as well so if it
doesn't happen event day it's sad
because you know you don't make it on
the on the you know Podium or whatever
but um there's always time to debate
afterwards yeah yeah I will say so I
also did this event basically solo um
and that was the first solo event I've
done in a long time um I usually lean
pretty heavy on collaborations because I
really like collaborations and I think
they're good opportunities but to be
quite honest when you do a lot of
collaboration it's really just like
sitting around waiting for somebody else
to come up with something and being like
hey I have this thing and you're like I
can help with that I think for you you
know one of the areas you shine is is as
an exploitation you know like like
there's there's a lot of things that
there's a different skill set from you
know exploiting a bug exploiting a weird
functionality and finding that weird
functionality finding the asset that's
going to give you weird function it's
not necessarily Recon right you know
Recon could be finding the asset and
that sort of thing understanding what is
weird in an application really requires
a more intimate knowledge of the
application and then you take that and
you say hey Joel this is why it's weird
this is what it would be cool if it
could do and then you know when you have
strong exploitation ISS like yourself in
you know that you can collaborate with
it works out really well yeah um but
when you when you spend a long long time
on collaboration some of those other
skills get a little rusty too y um which
is which is tricky and and something you
got to go in and be like okay I'm
self-aware of that I got to shake that
off and be a little bit more resilient
in that regard you know yeah it's going
to take more time it's gonna yeah
absolutely I I I dealt with a lot of
that during this event and the goal
thing um I think that's one area I
probably could have done better I didn't
set as many goals this event which I
wish I had I set a couple like soft
goals like I I I definitely set more
soft goals than it did hard goals and I
wish I would have gone for more like
hard goals like really go after like I
want to do this thing I want an atto or
I want to byass whatever like and just
go go go at that I think it might have
helped a little bit with the focus and
sort of the direction of my hacking yeah
um and the one soft goal that I did
pursue it didn't really pan out for you
know was just implemented securely um so
sometimes you run into that and youens
you did snag the flag yeah yeah which is
good um so you at least got something to
show for it uh but yeah that that goal
that goal oriented mentality is
important and then you've also got some
I don't know if you want to talk about
the thing but you've also got something
else going on right now taking a lot of
time selling a house buying a house yeah
I'm moving moving across the country so
I'm getting them on the East Coast so
we're going back to East Coast we're
going to recording the same time zone
eventually it's going to be clutch and
actually there there's direct flights
between where I live and where Joel
lives twice per day y so we could hop
down for an episode hop back and it'
only be like 100 bucks y so that would
be super clutch I'm very excited to have
you back on the East Coast yes so I'm
I'm looking forward to like four to five
months from now when hopefully
everything is a lot more chill I moved
in I am not dealing with constant chaos
this whole year has just been crazy man
from plumbing problems to house sales to
just non-stop so yeah I'm uh I'm hoping
this is this is uh the Bad Karma side of
the year and then the rest it can only
go up from here right so the so another
thing that comes to mind about this
event is um when you're working on a
company that's very big and has a lot of
different components and pieces to it
looking at o is absolutely essential
look at understanding the O flow very
intimately is super important because um
especially when you've got companies
that are are buying other companies and
you know sort of duct taping them into
their own INF structure um that off
piece is is really uh really tricky to
implement properly and uh and there's
also a lot of things you can do with
open redirects and with client side
stuff and oh can I leak this specific
piece of information by any of six
different ways you know and if you can
then you've really got a serious bug
well I know I mean you said I'm a good
exploitation you're at least as good as
I am if not better bro because like to
be honest like in order to exploit those
kind of bugs you have to have an
intimate level of understanding of the
application you got have gadgets right
because like you might look at the auth
implementation and be like this this is
just standard oo like I don't know what
to make of this right but like you have
to try stuff you have to know what to
try you have to have sort of that that
Playbook of things to be testing things
that you've seen before things that
you've seen around the app as well like
other areas of login that you might be
able to try and without that knowledge
like you're just going to walk up to be
like this looks like oo next yeah
absolutely the the knowledge of gadgets
and um the whole process and where it
might break down between all of these
different third parties vendors you know
Sister applications all of that sort of
thing one of the things that's that's
very interesting from the oath
perspective is is first party oath
applications where you don't have to
approve consent and third-party
applications um where you know somebody
can sign up and say I want to use XYZ
Target for single sign on or whatever um
and something that I've been seeing a
lot even outside of this event is like
look very granularly at those flows and
see if you can make any of them overlap
because the the first party flows often
don't require you know any sort of user
interaction to release information uh
and the third parties do and you can you
know sign up for your own third party
application so uh that's another really
a really cool area of interest that I've
been kind of peing my interest lately
yeah um and then and then also and this
is more relating to things before the
event but also things I've been hearing
about the event
looking very closely at any third-party
software that is being brought into a
hypers secure environment if you're
dealing with a Target that really takes
security seriously um they may have a
lot of their their own on lock yeah
you know and you may not be able to do
much with that but um when they say okay
I'm going to bring into you know my
application this little weird feature
this little Analytics tool or this
little you know thing you know little
widget y um then a lot of times they
expose themselves to undo risk and they
don't do enough security code review and
you know threat modeling on those
specific pieces of software I I'm
talking to you Joel I'm talking I'm
talking to myself and and I'm talking to
the audience you know I know you know
this well I mean honestly like and just
to highlight sort of
like whenever I see a company Implement
something from the ground up that is
like a big red flag for me especially if
it's something that's common right if I
see somebody reimplementing that's true
the flip side of this is very true as
well samel SSO like any of that that's
like weird to me I'm like why did why
didn't they just use some provider like
where did they mess up because did they
read the RFC like what you know how how
deep did they go on this and where can I
find you know one little crack that I
can exploit yeah it's kind of like a
catch22 right because if you use a third
party you know maybe they're you know
let's say samel like you said samel is
their Sam's their thing right um
and you know you'd assume that their
implementation would be better than your
sort of you know offthe cuff
implementation but on the other side you
don't know because you can't see the
code so it's like it's like okay do I
trust this or do I not trust this that
is one of those things that draws me in
all the time I get so distracted by
things cuz I'm like we've talked about
this I'm a big dopamine Hunter so like
whatever's like pulling my attention
I'll just like follow that and that uh
that caught me a couple times during
this event like they they were using a
specific um especially in a highly
infuscated environment they were using a
specific tool for obfuscation that had
really was peing my interest and so I
kept getting pulled off to the side like
oh how is this working oh maybe I can
find a way to like systemically figure
how that and it was just like not really
relevant but I kept it was like giving
me so much dopamine that I was just like
oh let me I just got to figure out how
this thing works like I don't even care
if there's a bug here I just want to
know how it works like oh go you know
and um and this is why this is why when
we work together it it works really well
cuz i' be like Joel are you staring at
that end point there's no bug there Joel
like there's not even a hint of a bug
there he's like no I need to understand
it right and so even if I see Sam like
say I see like somebody's using like you
know OCTA or whatever for S I'm like
maybe I can maybe I can break OCTA
like I am s like maybe TCP is the issue
here I think maybe there's a fundamental
hdp core problem oh my gosh those those
sort of things exist um oh this is such
a great tip and I got to shout out Matan
be for this one cuz he showed it to me
um and I went and read the HTML 5 spec
last night because I was so intrigued by
this did you know that image i m a g is
a separate element from IMG no well it
is for SVG right but if you put don't
have it in an SVG context the browser
Auto changes image to IMG wait what CLI
yeah in the browser so so it's like okay
you know how many things can we bypass
with that because you know there's so
many things image instead of image
exactly and they're like oh this is an
invalid HTML tag you know the outside of
SVG or something like that and it's
literally it's crazy you go to your
browser you type in image and you can
even put on you know source and on on
air handles and that sort of thing HML
thing yeah it says specifically in the
spec and it's hilarious too if you go to
the spec it says uh change the tokens
tag to image and then it says in this is
in the um in
the uh in the HTML body section uh uh
what you should do when you run into a
specific thing and it says don't ask is
what it say it literally says in Quotes
no way it says in quotes don't ask and
then it was funny you know cuz I was
like ah man I got to find more of these
you know if there's any of these other
weird little things nothing else and but
I went through and it was funny it says
if you encounter the sarcas sarcasm tag
take a deep breath and move along is
what it says dude I like oh wow how is
the HTML 5 spec actually an engaging
read like it's like this is great dude I
mean so shout out to the HTML 5 people
that was it was I I laughed I chuckled a
couple times so funny dude now I kind of
want to go read through it too you
reminded me of the time when when we
were looking into that um uh what was it
the body tag or something the there was
like that weird thing oh with meta or
base tag in the body tag that was super
weird yeah that should not work
according to the spec but the that's the
thing man I really wish um Google Chrome
or or like chromium would release a htl
5 as implemented by
chromium spec so it's like it's just a
description but it's how they've
actually implemented it in chromium
right because otherwise you've got to go
and read this you know see yeah C code
that's there yeah dude there are so many
things that that on that like that sort
of aspect of stuff that like I have to
hold myself back from the dopamine on
think because like um we were when we
were talking with Yousef right we were
talking about like the browser will
decide whether or not the user has
clicked on something to determine
whether or not like an xss should pop
right and it's like how does it how does
it determine that I've clicked on
something that I've done an action like
how is it actually doing that how does
the browser determine that like I
clicked it instead of something else C
dude they're in for such a good episode
man I can't even it's going to be so
good you guys he
drops Google Chrome bugs on the Pod it's
like it's amazing he's just like oh yeah
there's this bug I had in Chrome like he
like you know this common feature that
everybody uses it's such a great
implementation awesome awesome stuff uh
all righty man um I'm exhausted let's go
down and see if they're it seems like
they've paid a couple more bugs so let's
go let's cut it for now and go check in
on that awesome that's the Pod dude all
right that's the Pod thanks y'all
peace